<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Enca</string>
    <string name="enter_name">Benutzername</string>
    <string name="items">Artikel</string>
    <string name="login_confirm">Anmeldung</string>
    <string name="login_interfacelanguage"> Schnittstellensprache</string>
    <string name="login_contentlanguage">Inhaltsparache</string>
    <string name="rooms">Zimmer</string>
    <string name="search">Suchen</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Suchen</string>
    <string name="login_namehint">Gib deinen Namen ein</string>
    <string name="login_welcome">Was möchten Sie heute zu reinigen ? </string>
    <string name="usercenter_interfacelanguage"> Schnittstellensprache</string>
    <string name="usercenter_contentlanguage"> Inhaltsprache</string>
    <string name="usercenter">User Center</string>
    <string name="usercenter_namehint">Benutzername</string>
    <string name="noinput">Bitte Namen eingeben</string>
    <string name="reset_confirm"> Bestätigen</string>
    <string name="inputinvalid"> Eingabe ungültig</string>
    <string name="resetdialog"> Einstellung bestätigen</string>
    <string name="resetdialogmessage">Sind Sie sicher, dass Sie die Einstellung zu ändern ?</string>
    <string name="exitinformation"> Sind Sie sicher, dass Sie ENCA zu beenden</string>
    <string name="exittitle"> Beenden Achtung</string>
    <string name="cleaningagent_descriptionhint"> Beschreibung</string>
    <string name="cleaningagent_instructionhint">Anweisung</string>
    <string name="cleaningagent_locationhint">Ort</string>
    <string name="cleaningagent_ratehint">Bewertung</string>
    <string name="cleaningagent_typehint"> Art</string>
    <string name="cleaningagent_taghint"> Etikett Verbunden</string>
    <string name="promt">Wähle  Sprache</string>
    <string name="chooselanguage">Wählen Sprache</string>
    <string name="detail">Detail Information</string>
    <string name="tags">Etikett</string>
    <string name="hey">Hey</string>
    <string name="firstlogin_welcome"> Willkommen!</string>
    <string-array name="language_type">
        <item>English</item>
        <item>Deutsch</item>
        <item>中文</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="contentlanguage_prompt">Wir würden Sie verfügbaren Agenten in einem bestimmten Land Reinigung empfehlen .</string>
    <string name="interfacelanguage_prompt"> Diese Einstellung würde die Sprache der Benutzeroberfläche beeinflussen.</string>
    <string name="login_about">The MIT License (MIT)  Copyright (c) 2016 ENCA group.  Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the \"Software\"), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:  The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.  THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED \"AS IS\", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.</string>
    <string name="login_description">Software Description: Overwhelmed by various kinds of cleaning agents or having trouble identifying cleaning agents in a foreign country? ENCA, helps you choose the right cleaning agent.(Only China and Germany are available now, more countries are (not) coming!) ENCA provides you a platfrom with massive cleaning agent on record where you can search, add, modify, rate and comment on local cleaning agents. With our sophisticated tag system, finding the right cleaning agent is just a few clicks away. Ready to do some cleaning? Try out ENCA now!</string>
    <string name="login_logo_hint">Drücken, Erfahren Sie mehr über uns</string>
    <string name="login_personinformation">ENCA group:  Haoze Zhang Zhaowen Gong Zeling Wu Xiaoqi Ma</string>
    <string name="aboutus">Über uns</string>
</resources>